- 你好啊  迪吉  - 你好啊  鲁尼
- What's up, Diggie? - What's up, Rooney?
你的头发怎么了
'Sup with your hair?
你不会只听了我爸啰嗦几句
You did not get a haircut
就把头发理了吧
just because my dad told you to.
不  怎么会
No. Not at all.
我只是觉得头发太长罢了  你认为他会喜欢我的新发型么
I totally needed a trim. Do you think he'll like it?
迪吉  你可不能对他言听计从啊
Diggie, you can't let him push you around like this.
我是说  尽管你之前的头发是一团乱麻
I mean, your hair was a hot mess,
但这不是重点啊
but that's not the point.
我根本控制不住  行不  我想让他喜欢我啊
I can't help it, okay? I want him to like me.
他可是你爸  而我们俩是
He's your dad. And you and me are...
管它是什么呢
Whatever we are.
对啊  管它呢
Totally. Whatever.
呃  你需要找一个
Um... you just need to find something
你和我爸都喜欢的爱好  以此来拉近关系
that you and my dad both like and bond over that.
噢  对  太好了  让我看看
Oh, yeah, okay, great. Let's see.
他喜欢对我大吼大叫
He likes growling at me.
你知道他还喜欢什么吗
You know what else he likes...
烧烤
barbecuing.
烤肉架确实比大嗓门好多了
Grilling sure beats growling.
而且  如果他开始喜欢我了
And, if he starts to like me,
我就可以帮你准备驾照考试了
I could help you prep for your driver's test.
哎呀呀
Aww.
真贴心啊
That's so sweet.
老爸你好啊
Hey, Dad.
我跟你开玩笑呢  亲  哈哈
Dude, I'm kidding. Ha ha.
但他可不会开玩笑
But he won't be.